{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who%20holds%20the%20record%20for%20the%20most%20career%20home%20runs%20in%20Major%20League%20Baseball%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Barry%20Bonds",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Hank%20Aaron",
        "Babe%20Ruth",
        "Alex%20Rodriguez"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20team%20holds%20the%20record%20for%20the%20most%20World%20Series%20championships%3F",
      "correct_answer": "New%20York%20Yankees",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Boston%20Red%20Sox",
        "Los%20Angeles%20Dodgers",
        "San%20Francisco%20Giants"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who%20was%20the%20first%20player%20to%20break%20the%20color%20barrier%20in%20MLB%20by%20joining%20the%20Brooklyn%20Dodgers%20in%201947%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Jackie%20Robinson",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Satchel%20Paige",
        "Willie%20Mays",
        "Hank%20Aaron"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20pitcher%20holds%20the%20record%20for%20the%20most%20career%20strikeouts%20in%20MLB%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Nolan%20Ryan",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Randy%20Johnson",
        "Roger%20Clemens",
        "Greg%20Maddux"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20term%20for%20a%20home%20run%20hit%20when%20the%20batter%20hits%20all%20three%20bases%20in%20succession%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Inside-the-Park%20Home%20Run",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Grand%20Slam",
        "Bunt%20Home%20Run",
        "Moonshot%20Home%20Run"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20player%20holds%20the%20record%20for%20the%20most%20career%20hits%20in%20MLB%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Pete%20Rose",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Hank%20Aaron",
        "Ty%20Cobb",
        "Stan%20Musial"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20team%20won%20the%20first%20ever%20World%20Series%20in%20Major%20League%20Baseball%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Boston%20Americans",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Chicago%20White%20Sox",
        "New%20York%20Giants",
        "Philadelphia%20Athletics"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20player%20holds%20the%20record%20for%20the%20highest%20career%20batting%20average%20in%20MLB%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Ty%20Cobb",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Babe%20Ruth",
        "Ted%20Williams",
        "Honus%20Wagner"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20term%20for%20a%20pitcher%20who%20throws%20the%20ball%20with%20his%20left%20hand%20in%20baseball%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Southpaw",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Slurve",
        "Knuckleballer",
        "Submariner"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20term%20for%20the%20hit%20in%20baseball%20where%20the%20batter%20advances%20to%20third%20base%20safely%20in%20one%20play%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Triple",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Double",
        "Home%20Run",
        "Bunt"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
